const quizData = [
  {
    question:
      "What is the storage service provided by AWS that offers scalable object storage?",
    options: ["Amazon S3", "Amazon EC2", "Amazon RDS", "Amazon EBS"],
    answer: "Amazon S3",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which AWS service is used for deploying and managing containerized applications?",
    options: ["Amazon ECS", "AWS Lambda", "Amazon S3", "Amazon SQS"],
    answer: "Amazon ECS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the AWS service that provides a fully managed relational database?",
    options: [
      "Amazon RDS",
      "Amazon DynamoDB",
      "Amazon Redshift",
      "Amazon Aurora",
    ],
    answer: "Amazon RDS",
  },
  {
    question: "Which AWS service is used for serverless computing?",
    options: ["AWS Lambda", "Amazon EC2", "Amazon S3", "Amazon ECS"],
    answer: "AWS Lambda",
  },
  {
    question: "What AWS service is used for real-time streaming of data?",
    options: ["Amazon Kinesis", "Amazon S3", "Amazon Glacier", "Amazon RDS"],
    answer: "Amazon Kinesis",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which AWS service is designed for building conversational interfaces (chatbots)?",
    options: [
      "Amazon Lex",
      "Amazon Polly",
      "Amazon Transcribe",
      "Amazon Rekognition",
    ],
    answer: "Amazon Lex",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the AWS service that provides managed file storage?",
    options: ["Amazon EFS", "Amazon S3", "Amazon Glacier", "Amazon EBS"],
    answer: "Amazon EFS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which AWS service enables you to run code in response to events without provisioning servers?",
    options: ["AWS Lambda", "Amazon EC2", "Amazon ECS", "Amazon RDS"],
    answer: "AWS Lambda",
  },
  {
    question: "What AWS service provides scalable NoSQL databases?",
    options: [
      "Amazon DynamoDB",
      "Amazon RDS",
      "Amazon Redshift",
      "Amazon Aurora",
    ],
    answer: "Amazon DynamoDB",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which AWS service allows you to securely control access to AWS resources?",
    options: ["AWS IAM", "AWS KMS", "Amazon S3", "Amazon RDS"],
    answer: "AWS IAM",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What AWS service is used for machine learning and artificial intelligence?",
    options: [
      "Amazon SageMaker",
      "Amazon Rekognition",
      "Amazon Lex",
      "Amazon Transcribe",
    ],
    answer: "Amazon SageMaker",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which AWS service is used for managing and automating infrastructure deployments?",
    options: ["AWS CloudFormation", "AWS OpsWorks", "Amazon ECS", "Amazon S3"],
    answer: "AWS CloudFormation",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the AWS service that provides scalable data warehousing?",
    options: [
      "Amazon Redshift",
      "Amazon DynamoDB",
      "Amazon RDS",
      "Amazon Aurora",
    ],
    answer: "Amazon Redshift",
  },
  {
    question: "Which AWS service provides managed blockchain networks?",
    options: [
      "Amazon Managed Blockchain",
      "Amazon RDS",
      "Amazon S3",
      "Amazon DynamoDB",
    ],
    answer: "Amazon Managed Blockchain",
  },
  {
    question: "What AWS service is used for content delivery and caching?",
    options: [
      "Amazon CloudFront",
      "Amazon Route 53",
      "Amazon S3",
      "Amazon VPC",
    ],
    answer: "Amazon CloudFront",
  },
];

export default quizData;
